# Copyright (c) Symbian Software Ltd 2009. All rights reserved.
# AuthServer Repository. Contains authentication strength alias defintion.
# 2001ea7f.txt

cenrep
version 1

[PlatSec]
# AuthServer repository can be accessed/modified only by AuthServer.
sid_rd=0x102740FC  sid_wr=0x102740FC 

[Main]
# The default plugin for the system is defined for the first key (0x00000000).This must be a EAuthKnowledge type plugin id 
# and must have a default data associated with it. The default plugin cannot be an expression / plugin type/ alias.
#
#   
# Each authentication strength alias is also defined here.
# A typical authentication strength alias includes the following data parts:
# Authentication Strength Alias: The various authentication strengths like strong, medium, weak etc.
# Authentication Strength Alias Expression: The authentication expression describing each strength.
# The expression could contain plugin id, plugin type, strength alias or a combination of any of them.
#
# With this repository file, it is possible to insert up to 256 default authentication aliases definition.
# The number of the records must be defined in the second key (0x00000100).
# * 0x00000200 - 0x000002FF range is reserved for Authentication Strength Aliases. The name of the first
# authentication strength must be defined with 0x00000200, the second one is 0x00000201, and so on.
# * 0x00000300 - 0x000003FF range is reserved for the authentication expressions corressponding to each authentication
# strength described above. 


#Default system-wide plugin 
0x00000000	int	0

# Key for 'Number of Authentication Strength Aliases'- Must be the number of authentication aliases defined.
0x00000100	int 	4

# Key for authentication strength aliases.
0x00000200	string 	"strong"
0x00000201	string 	"fast"
0x00000202	string 	"medium"
0x00000203	string 	"weak"

# Key for the authentication expressions corressponding to the above defined strengths.
0x00000300	string 	""
0x00000301	string 	""
0x00000302	string 	""
0x00000303	string 	""
